<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<moblies>
 <moblie>
    <title>IPhone X</title>
    <price>£999</price>
    <description>
      With Apple iPhone X, the device is the display. An all-new 5.8-inch Super Retina display employs
      new techniques and technology to precisely follow the curves of the design. The OLED screen delivers
      accurate, stunning colours, true blacks, high brightness, and a 1,000,000 to 1 contrast ratio.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>Huawei P20</title>
    <image>huaweiP20.png</image>
    <price>£599</price>
    <description>
      Engineered in collaboration with Leica, the dual lens (20MP and 12MP) camera of the Huawei P20 is
      infused with AI technology to ensure that you capture true-to-life photographs every time. The AI
      stabilisation feature also enables users to snap blur-free handheld shots in low light and record
      the details of moving actions.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>IPhone 6</title>
    <image>iphone6.png</image>
    <price>£199</price>
    <description>
      The iPhone 6s has a stunning 4.7″ display with responsive 3D Touch
      that can sense the pressure you apply to the screen and act accordingly.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>IPhone XR</title>
    <image>iphoneXR.png</image>
    <price>£749</price>
    <description>
      The new Liquid Retina display on iPhone XR is the most advanced LCD ever,
      backlit so the screen stretches into the corners. So now you can see true-to-life
      colours from one beautiful edge to the other.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>Moto E5</title>
    <image>motoE5.png</image>
    <price>£299</price>
    <description>
      The E5 Play has a large 5.3″ screen with 18:9 Max Vision display so your photos and videos look fantastic.
      The E5 Play has an advanced 8MP camera with autofocus that works well even in low light conditions,
      so you can take great photos whatever time it is.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>Samsung S9</title>
    <image>samsungs9.png</image>
    <price>£900</price>
    <description>
      With a specially-designed dual aperture lens that works like the iris of a human eye,
      the Samsung Galaxy S9’s camera finds light even in the dark – capturing your photographs
      in super low or super bright lighting conditions, so you can take photographs at any time of day.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>Nokia 5</title>
    <image>nokia5.png</image>
    <price>£110</price>
    <description>
      With a beautifully designed 5"2 HD display the Nokia 5 comes with a 13MP camera
      more than capable of taking beautiful snapshots.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>Samsung J6</title>
    <image>samsungj6.png</image>
    <price>£265</price>
    <description>
      Stated saving achieved over the duration of credit agreement; discount applied
      to monthly payments and will vary dependent on agreement length. While stocks last.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>Sony Xperia XA2</title>
    <image>sonyxperiaxa2.png</image>
    <price>£305</price>
    <description>
      Shoot photos and videos with outstanding colour and clarity using the
      Xperia XA2’s 23MP camera with Sony’s light sensitive Exmor RSTM  for mobile
      sensor plus 4K video recording. Or create fun, slow-motion videos in HD.
    </description>
 </moblie>
 <moblie>
    <title>Alcatel 3V</title>
    <image>alcatel3v.png</image>
    <price>£99</price>
    <description>
      The 12MP front camera on the Alcatel 3V has a breathtaking depth of field so you can capture
      all the details, while the 5MP rear camera is perfect for snapping selfies.
    </description>
 </moblie>
</moblies>
